<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- 
  -   assgn2.xml for Assignment #2
  -   Sung Min Yoon
  -   991471303
 -->
<yoosungm>
    <title>Assignment 2</title>
    <studentNumber program="Computer Programmer">991471303</studentNumber>
    <studentName login="yoosungm">Sung Min Yoon</studentName>
   
    <bookstore>
        <name url="https://www.chapters.indigo.ca/en-ca/">Chapters</name>
        <icon>ui-icon-chapters</icon>
    </bookstore>
    <bookstore>
        <name url="https://www.biblio.com/">Biblio</name>
        <icon>ui-icon-biblio</icon>
    </bookstore>
    <bookstore>
        <name url="https://www.abebooks.com/">AbeBooks</name>
        <icon>ui-icon-abebooks</icon>
    </bookstore>
    
    <book category="Business and Finance">
        <bookTitle inventoryID="9781554686360" price="19.55">Freakonomics</bookTitle>
        <descripton>Freakonomics is a ground-breaking collaboration between Levitt and Stephen J. Dubner, an award-winning author and journalist. They usually begin with a mountain of data and a simple, unasked question. Some of these questions concern life-and-death issues; others have an admittedly freakish quality. Thus the new field of study contained in this book: Freakonomics. (freakonomics.com)</descripton>
        <image>freakonomics.jpg</image>        
    </book>    
    <book category="Legal Thriller">
        <bookTitle inventoryID="9780440245933" price="13.22">The Pelican Brief</bookTitle>
        <descripton>In suburban Georgetown, a killer’s Reeboks whisper on the floor of a posh home. In a seedy D.C. porno house, a patron is swiftly garroted to death. The next day America learns that two of its Supreme Court justices have been assassinated. And in New Orleans, a young law student prepares a legal brief. (Chapters)</descripton>
        <image>pelicanbrief.jpg</image>        
    </book>
    <book category="Legal Thriller">
        <bookTitle inventoryID="9780345531957" price="13.50">The Partner</bookTitle>
        <descripton>Once he was a well-liked, well-paid young partner in a thriving Mississippi law firm. Then Patrick Lanigan stole ninety million dollars from his own firm—and ran for his life. For four years, he evaded men who were rich and powerful, and who would stop at nothing to find him. Then, inevitably, on the edge of the Brazilian jungle, they finally tracked him down. (Chapters)</descripton>
        <image>thepartner.jpg</image>        
    </book>
    <book category="Legal Thriller">
        <bookTitle inventoryID="9780440245926" price="12.49">The Firm</bookTitle>
        <descripton>When Mitch McDeere signed on with Bendini, Lambert &amp; Locke of Memphis, he thought that he and his beautiful wife, Abby, were on their way. The firm leased him a BMW, paid off his school loans, arranged a mortgage, and hired the McDeeres a decorator. Mitch should have remembered what his brother Ray–doing fifteen years in a Tennessee jail–already knew: You never get nothing for nothing. Now the FBI has the lowdown on Mitch’s firm and needs his help. Mitch is caught between a rock and a hard place, with no choice–if he wants to live. (Chapters)</descripton>
        <image>thefirm.jpg</image>        
    </book>
    <book category="Computers">
        <bookTitle inventoryID="9780201000238" price="86.47">Data Structures and Algorithms</bookTitle>
        <descripton>The authors' treatment of data structures in Data Structures and Algorithms is unified by an informal notion of "abstract data types," allowing readers to compare different implementations of the same concept. Algorithm design techniques are also stressed and basic algorithm analysis is covered. Most of the programs are written in Pascal. (Chapters)</descripton>
        <image>dataalgo.jpg</image>        
    </book>    
    <book category="Computers">
        <bookTitle inventoryID="9781119017929" price="25.56">Android App Development for Dummies</bookTitle>
        <description>Create seriously cool apps for the latest Android smartphones and tablets. Adapt your existing apps for use on an Android device. Start working with programs and tools to create Android apps. Publish your apps to the Google Play Store. Whether you're a new or veteran programmer, Android App Development For Dummies will have you up and running with the ins and outs of the Android platform in no time. (Chapters)</description>
        <image>androiddummies.jpg</image>        
    </book>
    <book category="Computers">
        <bookTitle inventoryID="9781491971949" price="48.23">Mastering Ethereum: Building Smart Contracts and Dapps</bookTitle>
        <descripton>By bridging the world of cloud computing, grid computing, and blockchains, Ethereum has created a massive decentralized computing platform that many people are calling a "world computer." Ethereum has also spawned a rapidly growing ecosystem of software startups vying to build decentralized applications, known as "dapps". (Chapters)</descripton>
        <image>ethmaster.jpg</image>        
    </book>
    <book category="Computers">
        <bookTitle inventoryID="9781250114570" price="30.63">The Truth Machine: The Blockchain and the Future of Everything</bookTitle>
        <descripton>"Views differ on bitcoin, but few doubt the transformative potential of Blockchain technology. The Truth Machine is the best book so far on what has happened and what may come along. It demands the attention of anyone concerned with our economic future." -Lawrence H. Summers, Charles W. Eliot University Professor and President Emeritus at Harvard, Former Treasury Secretary</descripton>
        <image>truthmachine.jpg</image>        
    </book>
</yoosungm>